blowjobs.com 2018-06-13

# Blowjobs.com

                                                 Blowjobs.com
                                                 Privacy Policy
                                         Last Updated: August 14, 2017
Internet Key, Inc., a New Jersey corporation (the “Company”), respects your privacy and is committed to
protecting it through this privacy policy (the “policy”). This policy describes the types of information the
Company may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website located at
www.Blowjobs.comm (the “Website”) and the Company’s practices for collecting, using, keeping,
protecting, and disclosing that information.
This policy applies to information the Company collects:
     •   On the Website (including desktop and mobile versions).
     •   In email, text, and other electronic messages between you and the Company.
     •   When you interact with the Company’s advertising and applications on third-party websites and
         services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy.
     •   When you interact with the Website through third-party social media platforms.
It does not apply to information collected by:
     •   the Company offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by the
         Company or any third party (including the Company’s affiliates and subsidiaries); or
     •   any third party (including the Company’s affiliates and subsidiaries), including through any
         application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from (or on) the
         Website.
Important: Please read this policy carefully to understand the Company’s policies and practices regarding
your information and how the Company will treat it. If you do not agree with the Company’s policies and
practices, your choice is not to use the Website. By accessing or using the Website, you agree to this
policy and consent to the Company’s collection, use, disclosure, retention, and protection of your
personal information as described in this policy. The Company may change this policy on one or more
occasions. The Company will consider your continued use of the Website after the Company makes
changes as your acceptance of the changes, so please check this policy frequently for updates.
1. Are minors welcome?
The Website is not intended for anyone under 18-years old. You will only access the Website or register
 for an account if (1) you are at least 18-years old and (2) have reached the age of majority where you live.
 The Company prohibits all persons who do not meet the age requirements from accessing the Website.
 Minors must not access the Website or use its services.

The Company does not knowingly collect or solicit any information or data from anyone under 18-years
 old. The Website and its content are not directed at persons under 18-years old. If the Company learns
 that it has collected personal information from a person under 18-years old, the Company will delete that
 information as quickly as possible. If you believe that the Company might have any information from or
 about a person under 18-years old, please contact the Company at privacy@internetkey.com.
Section 230 Notice: In accordance with 47 U.S.C. § 230(d), you are notified that parental control
protections (including computer hardware, software, or filtering services) are commercially available that
may assist in limiting access to material that is harmful to minors. You may find information about
providers of these protections on the Internet by searching “parental control protection” or similar terms.
If minors have access to your computer, please restrain their access to sexually explicit material by using
any of the following products, which the Company provides for informational purposes only and does not
endorse: CYBERsitter™ | Net Nanny® | CyberPatrol | ASACP.
2. What types of information does the Company collect about you and how is it collected?
The Company may collect several types of information from and about users of the Website, including
 information:
     •    by which you may be personally identified, including your username, password, email address, or
          any other information that the Company collects that is defined as personal or personally
          identifiable information under law (“personal information”);
     •    that is about you but individually does not identify you, including your age, gender, location, and
          any other optional information you provide about yourself; or
     •    about your Internet connection, the equipment you use to access the Website, and usage details.
The Company collects this information:
     •    Directly from you when you provide it to the Company.
     •    Automatically as you navigate through the Website. Information collected automatically may
          include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies, web beacons, and
          other tracking technologies.
     •    From third parties, for example, the Company’s business partners.
Information You Provide to the Company
The information the Company collects on or through the Website may include:
     •    Information that you provide by filing in forms on the Website. This includes information provided
          at the time of registering to use the Website or requesting further services. The Company may also
          ask you for information when you report a problem with the Website.
                                                        2

     •   Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact the
         Company.
     •   Your responses to surveys that the Company might ask you to complete for research purposes.
     •   Details of transactions you carry out through the Website and of the fulfillment of your requests.
     •   Your search queries on the Website.
You also may provide information to be published or displayed (“posted”) on public areas of the Website,
 or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties (collectively, “user contributions”). Your user
 contributions are posted on the Website and transmitted to others at your own risk. Although you may
 be able to set certain privacy settings for this information by logging into your account (if you have one),
 please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, the Company cannot
 control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your user
 contributions. Thus, the Company cannot and does not guarantee that your user contributions will not be
 viewed by unauthorized persons.
Information the Company Collects through Automatic Data Collection Technologies
As you navigate through and interact with the Website, the Company may use automatic data collection
 technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns,
 including:
     •   Details of your visits to the Website, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other
         communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.
     •   Information about your computer and Internet connection, including your IP address, operating
         system, and browser type.
     •   Information about your mobile device and Internet connection, including the device’s unique
         device identifier, IP address, operating system, browser type, mobile network information, and
         the device’s telephone number.
The Company also may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities over
 time and across third-party websites or other online services (behavioral tracking).
The information the Company collects automatically is statistical data and does not include personal
 information, but the Company may keep it or associate it with personal information the Company collects
 in other ways or receives from third parties. It helps the Company to improve the Website and to deliver
 a better and more personalized service, including by allowing the Company to:
     •   Estimate the Website’s audience size and usage patterns.
     •   Store information about your preferences, thus allowing the Company to customize the Website
         according to your individual interests.
                                                        3

    •   Speed up your searches.
    •   Recognize you when you return to the Website.
The technologies the Company uses for this automatic data collection may include:
    •   Cookies (or browser cookies). A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer.
        Your browser stores cookies in a manner associated with each website you visit. The Company
        uses cookies to enable its servers to recognize your browser and tells the Company how and when
         you visit the Website and use the services. For example, the Company uses session ID cookies,
         which makes it easier for you to navigate the Website. A session ID cookie expires when you close
         your browser. The Company also uses persistent cookies, which remain on your hard drive for an
         extended period. Persistent cookies may be used to store your login information and preferences.
         You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser.
         But if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of the Website. Unless you
         have adjusted your browser settings so that it will refuse cookies, the Company’s system will issue
         cookies when you direct your browser to the Website. If you want to learn more about cookies,
         please visit www.allaboutcookies.org or www.youronlinechoices.eu.
    •   Flash Cookies. Certain features of the Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to
        collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from, and on the Website.
        Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies. For
        information about managing your privacy and security settings for Flash cookies, you can access
        your Flash management tools from Adobe’s website.
    •   Web Beacons. Pages of the Website (and the Company’s emails) may contain small electronic files
        known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit
        the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages (or opened an email) and
        for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website
        content and verifying system and server integrity). If you want to learn more about web beacons,
        please visit www.allaboutcookies.org/web-beacons/.
The Company does not collect personal information automatically, but it may tie this information to
personal information about you that the Company collects from other sources or you provide to the
Company.
Third-party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Website are served by third parties,
including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third
parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect
information about you when you use the Website. The information they collect may be associated with
your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your
online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this
information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.
                                                      4

The Company does not control third-party tracking technologies or how third parties’ use them. If you
have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible
provider directly.
3. How does the Company use your information?
The Company may use the information that it collects about you or that you provide to the Company for
any of the following purposes:
    •   To provide, operate, maintain, improve, and promote the Website.
    •   To enable you to access and use the Website.
    •   To process and complete transactions, and send you related information.
    •   To send transactional messages, including responding to your comments, questions, and requests;
        providing customer service and support; and sending you technical notices, updates, security
        alerts, and support and administrative messages.
    •   To send promotional communications, such as providing you with information about services,
        features, newsletters, offers, promotions, contests, and events.
    •   To monitor and analyze trends, usage, and activities in connection with the Website and for
        marketing or advertising purposes.
    •   To investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions, unauthorized access to the Website, and other
        illegal activities.
    •   To personalize the Website content, features, or advertisements.
    •   In any other way the Company may describe when you provide the information.
    •   For any other purpose with your consent.
The Company may also use your information to contact you about the Company’s own and third parties’
goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want the Company to use your information
in this way, please send the Company an email at privacy@internetkey.com. For more information, see
What choices do you have about how the Company uses and discloses your information.
The Company may use the information it has collected from you to allow the Company to display
advertisements to its advertisers’ target audiences. Even though the Company does not disclose your
personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with
an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.
4. With whom does the Company share your information?
                                                      5

The Company may disclose aggregated information about its users, and information that does not identify
any individual, without restriction.
The Company may disclose personal information that it collects or you provide as described in this policy:
     • To the Company’s subsidiaries and affiliates.
     •   To contractors, service providers, and other third parties the Company uses to support its business
         and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use
         it only for the purposes for which the Company discloses it to them.
     •   To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization,
         dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all the Company’s assets, whether as a going
         concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information
         held by the Company about the Website’s users is among the assets transferred.
     •   To third parties to market their products or services to you if you have not opted out of these
         disclosures. The Company contractually requires these third parties to keep personal information
         confidential and use it only for the purposes for which the Company discloses it to them. For more
         information, see What choices do you have about how the Company uses and discloses your
         information.
     •   To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
     •   For any other purpose disclosed by the Company when you provide the information.
     •   With your consent.
The Company may also disclose your personal information:
     •   To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or
         regulatory request.
     •   To enforce or apply the Terms of Use Agreement and other agreements.
     •   If the Company believes disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or
         safety of the Company, its customers, or others.
5. When you put information about yourself on the Website, what do the other users see?
Other users can see your username and any information you post on your profile. Any information you
choose to give should reflect how much you want other users to know about you.
The Company recommends and encourages you to think carefully about the information you disclose
about yourself. The Company does not recommend that you put email addresses, URLs, phone numbers,
full name, mailing address, credit card details, identification numbers, drivers’ license details, or other
sensitive information in your profile, which is open to abuse and misuse.
                                                       6

Please be careful about posting sensitive details about yourself on your profile. While you may voluntarily
give this information to the Company when you create your profile, there is no requirement to do so.
Please remember that photographs or any video clips that you post on the Website (if allowed) may reveal
these kinds of sensitive personal data. Where you do upload, and choose to tell the Company sensitive
information about yourself, you are expressly consenting to the Company processing your information
and making it public to other users.
When you post information about yourself or use the communication features, the amount of personal
information you share is at your own risk. If you post anything that is inconsistent with the Terms of Use
Agreement, the Company may terminate your account.
Warning: Any personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data that you disclose through
the public online forums hosted on the Website may be collected and used by others. The Company
recommends caution when giving out personal information to others in these public online forums.
6. What choices do you have about how the Company uses and discloses your information?
The Company provides you the ability to exercise certain controls and choices regarding its collection, use,
and sharing of your information. In accordance with local law, your controls and choices may include:
    •   You may correct, update, and delete your account information.
    •   You may change your choices for subscriptions and newsletters.
    •   You may choose whether to receive offers from the Company.
    •   You may choose whether you receive targeted advertising from the Company or its third-party
        advertising partners.
7. How do you access and correct your information?
For personal information that the Company holds, the Company will provide you with access for any
purpose including to request that the Company correct the data if it is inaccurate or delete the data if the
Company is not required to retain it by law or for legitimate business purposes. The Company may decline
to process requests that are frivolous/vexatious, jeopardize the privacy of others, are extremely
impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required by local law.
8. How does the Company protect your personal information?
The Company has implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental
loss and from unauthorized access, use, change, and disclosure. All information you provide to the
Company is stored on its secure servers behind firewalls.
The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where the Company has given you (or
where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of the Website, you are responsible for
keeping this password confidential. The Company asks you not to share your password with anyone. In
                                                      7

addition, the Company urges you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the Website.
The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the Website.
No Security Guarantees. The transmission of information over the Internet is not completely secure.
Although the Company does its best to protect your personal information, the Company does not
guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to the Website or guarantee against all
unauthorized disclosure, alteration, or destruction of personal information. Any transmission of personal
information is at your own risk. The Company is not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings
or security measures contained on the Website.
9. Where is your personal information kept?
This policy is intended to cover collection of information on or through the Website from residents of the
United States. If you are visiting the Website from outside the United States, please be aware that your
information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where the Company’s
servers are located and the Company’s central database is operated. The data protection and other laws
of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. Please
be assured that the Company seeks to take reasonable steps to make sure that your privacy is protected.
By using the Company’s services, you acknowledge that your information may be transferred to the
Company’s facilities and those third parties with whom the Company shares it as described in this policy.
When you provide personal information to the Company through the Website, you consent to the
processing of your data in, and the transfer of your data to, the United States or any other country in
which the Company or its affiliates, subsidiaries, or service providers host these services.
10. Do Not Track Policy
Do Not Track (“DNT”) is a privacy preference that you can set in your browser. DNT is a way for you to
inform websites and services that you do not want certain information about your webpage visits
collected over time and across websites or online services. The Company is committed to providing you
with meaningful choices about the information it collects and that is why the Company provides you the
ability to opt out. But the Company does not recognize or respond to any DNT signals as the Internet
industry works toward defining exactly what DNT means, what it means to comply with DNT, and a
common approach to responding to DNT. For more information, visit www.allaboutdnt.com.
11. Your California Privacy Rights
If you are a California resident, you may have certain additional rights. California Civil Code Section
1798.83 permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information by the
Company to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. Further, if you are a California
resident and would like to opt out from the disclosure of your personal information to any third party for
direct marketing purposes, please send an email to privacy@internetkey.com. Please be advised that if
you opt out from permitting your personal information to be shared, you may still receive selected offers
directly from the Company in accordance with California law.
12. Links to Other Websites
                                                      8

The Website contains links to other websites. Please be aware that the Company is not responsible for
the content or privacy practices of those other websites. The Company encourages its customers to be
aware when they leave the Website and to read the privacy statements of any other website that collects
personally identifiable information.
13. No Rights of Third Parties
This policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal
information relating to users of the Website.
14. DMCA Takedown Requests
The Website complies with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA). If you reasonably believe that
your copyrighted work has been used or posted by a third party without your consent, you may follow the
instructions here on how to report it.
By submitting a copyright infringement notice or other communication (including communications about
content stored on or transmitted through the Website), you consent to have these communications
forwarded to the person or entity who stored, transmitted, or linked to the content addressed by your
communication, to facilitate a prompt resolution. The Company forwards DMCA infringement notices
(including any personally identifying information contained in the notices) as submitted to the Company
without any deletions.
15. Changes to Privacy Policy
Although most changes are likely to be minor, the Company may change this policy on one or more
occasions, and in its sole discretion. The Company encourages visitors to frequently check this page for
any changes to this policy. Your continued use of the Website after any change in this policy will constitute
your acceptance of the changes.
16. Contact Information
To ask questions or comment about this policy and the Company’s privacy practices, you may contact the
Company at privacy@internetkey.com.
                                                     9
